TEAM LUNIA REBORN

End-User License Agreement (EULA)
Last updated 06/10/2021

Please read this End-User License Agreement ("Agreement") carefully before clicking the "I Agree" button to proceed to the game.

By clicking the "I Agree" button, you are agreeing to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Agreement.

If you do not agree to the terms of this Agreement, click on the "I Don’t Agree" button and the game software will close automatically.

License
All rights are reserved to the original owners of LUNIA and LUNIA Z, this game is a tribute to the game that everyone loves but isn’t with us anymore, therefore you have non-exclusive, non-user transferable accounts, unless with some exceptions (read exceptions), to play this game in accordance with the terms of this Agreement.

Clauses and restrictions

1) Basic requirements
The user must make sure their personal computer has the minimum system requirements, that are listed on the web page https://lunia.com.br/ on the SYSTEM REQUIREMENTS tab, the user also agrees to the possible game actualizations, waiting times and things that may affect the quality of the game.

2) Age restriction
By the nature of this game, and complying with the Entertainment Software Rating Board (ESRB) and international entities that regulate online content, this game is classified as a “ACTION/RPG”, with cartoonish violence, comical mischief and/or suggestive topics, therefore this game shouldn’t be played by anyone under the age of 13. If the user is over 13 years old but under 18 years of age as of this date, they must be accompanied by their legal guardian or whoever exercises custody at the time of creating an account for the game, as well as when they are playing. In the event that the user is emancipated, they will be under the same conditions as any other user. Online interaction with other users is not rated, therefore the LUNIA REBORN staff aren’t liable about it.

3) User registration
In order to play the game the user must have an account that was created at the web page https://lunia.com.br/, in order to access the servers and play this game.

4. User identification
The user has the right to choose their username, but ANY name that contains any obscene words or that may offend other people's sex, gender, age, religion, international human rights, or any name that the LUNIA REBORN staff considers offensive will be removed/banned, depending of the offense.
The LUNIA REBORN staff encourages the user to not give any personal information through this game, and the staff isn’t liable for any harm that this may cause.

5) User accounts
The user must always keep their account confidential, the LUNIA REBORN staff isn’t liable for any damage that may occur if the user shares or sells their account. The user is exclusively responsible of how they manage their account.
In case the user loses access to their account, there’s a procedure to regain control. Please refer to the “Forgot password” section of the web page.

6) In game currency RCOINS
Besides the normal currency, there will exist RCOINS, that can only be acquired via donations in the web site https://lunia.com.br/, in the “RCOINS” section.
THIS WILL NOT BE REFUNDABLE.

7) Character customization 
The user can customize their character as they please, and can acquire items in game, trade or sell them for in game currency.
This will be, but not limited to:
*RCoins.
*Item bought with RCoins.
*Accessories.
*In game equipment.

8) Game interruptions and maintenance
The game is subject to periodical maintenance, so the service may go offline at times. Any interruptions will be announced either in game, on the server discord, or on the official web page, https://lunia.com.br/, these maintenances will be to ensure that the game runs properly and without any major problems to the users.

9) Misconduct, bad sportsmanship and offenses
The LUNIA REBORN staff commits all the available human resources to ensure that the game has the least amount of problems possible, and ensure the community that the game is free of any kind of misconduct, bad sportsmanship or offenses in game. 
The staff WILL NOT tolerate racist behavior of any kind. Any violation, depending on it, can result in an account suspension or termination with no responsibility to the LUNIA REBORN staff.
Please refer to the code of conduct section on the web page for more info.

10) Third party programs.
The use of third party programs, systems or any kind of program that enables the user to partake in any illegal activities or cheat in game will result in immediate account termination with no possibility to regain access to the account. This decision will be definitive and only under extreme circumstances will be taken into consideration and will be reviewed by all of the staff.

11) Game closure for legal reasons
The LUNIA REBORN staff can and will close the game services if there any government order or judicial order that determine that the game must close for the reasons that may be. This will be with no responsibility to the LUNIA REBORN STAFF.
In case there’s a cease of operations, the LUNIA REBORN staff will communicate to the game community 30 days before the closure via the web page and discord server.

12) Intellectual property and Copyright
All rights are reserved to the original owners of LUNIA and LUNIA Z. This is a tribute to the original game that closed so many years before. This game is running with a non-profit state of mind by the staff of LUNIA REBORN.

13) Health Warnings
WARNING: PHOTOSENSITIVITY/EPILEPSY SEIZURES
A very small percentage of individuals may experience epileptic seizures or blackouts when exposed to certain light patterns or flashing lights. Exposure to certain patterns or backgrounds on a television screen and/or monitor when playing video games may trigger epileptic seizures or blackouts in these individuals. These conditions may trigger previously undetected epileptic symptoms or seizures in persons who have no history of prior seizures or epilepsy. If you, or anyone in your family has an epileptic condition or has had seizures of any kind, consult your physician before playing. IMMEDIATELY DISCONTINUE use and consult your physician before resuming gameplay if you or your child experience any of the following health problems or symptoms:
*Dizziness
*Altered vision
*Eye or muscle twitches
*Loss of awareness
*Disorientation
*Seizures or Any involuntary movement or convulsion
RESUME GAME PLAY ONLY ON APPROVAL OF YOUR PHYSICIAN.
Use and handling of video games to reduce the likelihood of a seizure:
*Use in a well-lit area and keep as far away as possible from the television screen and/or monitor. Avoid large television screen and/or monitor. Use the smallest television screen and/or monitor. Avoid prolonged play. Take a 15-minute break during each hour of play. Avoid playing when you are tired or need sleep.
*Stop using the system immediately if you experience any of the following symptoms: lightheadedness, nausea, or a sensation similar to motion sickness, discomfort or pain in the eyes, ears, hands arms, or any other part of the body. If the condition persists, consult a doctor.

14) This EULA should always be interpreted with the laws of the country/state of which you are playing. The LUNIA REBORN STAFF isn’t responsible if you infringe any of your local laws.

15) Technical support
The Lunia Technical support will be available sundays from 6 pm to 7 pm east, to give technical support to the community via the Discord Server, in the following languages portuguese and english, if your language isn’t listed, please send an email to luniareborn@gmail.com, and a staff member will be in contact with you.

16) The LUNIA REBORN team is made up of people of different genders, sexual preferences, races and religious beliefs, so discrimination of any kind will not be tolerated.

W.C.F.- Legal Lime and Grammar Nazi Lime aka Gooby.